<?xml version="1.0"?>
<blogs>
<blog><author>Hazel Wyllie</author><date>Sat, 12 Mar 2016 13:42:04 +0000</date><title>Card Sorting</title><description>I went back to my users to help me decide which features would be the most important in the app and used the Card Sorting research technique to do this. Cards were printed out with 12 different possible app features on them. The users were asked to think about the features and rate in an&#x2026; </description><link>https://hazelwyllie.wordpress.com/2016/03/12/card-sorting/</link></blog><blog><author></author><date>Thu, 03 Mar 2016 19:54:05 +0000</date><title>Reporting button: inspiration and initial prototypes</title><description>Before starting sketching of the initial ideas for the reporting button, I looked into different elements&#xA0;that will have impact on the design. The types of handlebars used by cyclists can be narrowed down to four types: Cyclists-commuters usually use riser bars, while cyclists travelling longer distances usually have drop bars. Depending on the bike type [&#x2026;]</description><link>https://stronska.wordpress.com/2016/03/03/reporting-button-inspiration-and-initial-prototypes/</link></blog><blog><author>Petr Chutny</author><date>Mon, 29 Feb 2016 15:25:36 +0000</date><title>Chef &#x2013; Experience Prototype</title><description>In our Honours project, we are delivering two prototypes before the final one. For the MK1, I&#xA0;decided to create an experience prototype, using the &#x201C;Wizzard of Oz&#x201D; method...</description><link>http://petrchutny.cz/?p=1055</link></blog><blog><author>Iona Broadhurst</author><date>Wed, 17 Feb 2016 16:28:12 +0000</date><title>hickety-hackety</title><description>Inductive charging- chopped up a toothbrush because similar charging technologies. Wanted to look more in depth at the wireless transfer of energy. &#xA0; &#xA0; To put this in to context with the project, I moved on to hacking up some existing wireless chargers to see how they were wired up inside- component parts that were&#x2026; </description><link>https://ionabroadhurst.wordpress.com/2016/02/17/hickety-hackety/</link></blog><blog><author>Dean Taylor</author><date>Tue, 09 Feb 2016 13:24:42 +0000</date><title>Mood Boards</title><description>I&#x2019;ve been regularly updating &#x2018;mood boards&#x2019; as I move forward with this project. These boards actually help me think through common problems with the typical&#xA0;interface and remind me of how the more unusual devices come about. It&#x2019;s a way to keep excited about the project as well as drawing inspiration and ideas. Whilst at this [&#x2026;]</description><link>http://deantaylordesign.com/words/?p=338</link></blog><blog><author>Duncan's Chatter</author><date>Sun, 07 Feb 2016 19:52:29 +0000</date><title>The kit&#x2019;s physical form&#x2026;</title><description>I&#x2019;ve been playing around with what form the physical kit will take. I&#x2019;ve been working through form mostly using sketching and quick cardboard models before&#xA0;onto Solidworks. &#xA0; I drew up a number of ideas and made various forms before discussing them with classmates and also Chris. From here I moved onto Solidworks which was really [&#x2026;]</description><link>http://www.duncanstuartgordon.com/?p=805</link></blog><blog><author>Ciaran's Design Blog</author><date>Wed, 03 Feb 2016 15:21:16 +0000</date><title>Honours Year:  Early Design Language (22)</title><description>I made some stills which illustrate very early thinking regarding my design language for annotated video clips. The idea is the text/icons are simple overlays over the video...</description><link>http://socialdigital.dundee.ac.uk/~chynd/blog/?p=336</link></blog><blog><author>Andrew Stewart | Dundee</author><date>Mon, 26 Oct 2015 13:30:21 +0000</date><title>Welcome!</title><description>Welcome to my blog, started in October 2015 to map my fourth year as a Product Design student at DJCAD,&#x2026; </description><link>https://awjstewart.wordpress.com/2015/10/26/welcome/</link></blog><blog><author>Patrick Drabble</author><date></date><title>500 Miles</title><description></description><link>/?action=viewArticle</link></blog></blogs>
